# CURRICULUM VITAE

## **Mohit Sharma**

(Marketing Salesman)

Email ID- edward78626@gmail.com

**Contact No:** +91 7210203536

## **SUMMARY:**

Highly motivated, detailed oriented, quick learner, team player and energetic Marketing Salesman with 3+ years of experience, and finding innovative solutions for job efficiency Strong customer service & communication skills, flexible, dependable, and work very well with others as well as independently and productively manages heavy workloads, while focusing attention on accuracy and detail.

#### **COMPUTER SKILL:**

Microsoft office (MS Word, MS Excel)

Busy Accounting Software

E-commerce portal

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

❤ Field Boy in Blinkit Company
Oct 2022-till date

Salesman in Pitambari Products Pvt Ltd Sep 2021-Oct 2022

Product Lister of Various E-commerce Business Oct 2019- Sep 2021

in Drisha Trading Company.

#### **EDUCATION**

Passing Year-2013 High School 10th (C.B.S.E. Board)

Passing Year-2015 Intermediate 12th (C.B.S.E Board)

Passing Year-2019 Bachelor of Arts (University of Delhi)

### **PERSONAL DETAILS:**

**Date Of Birth** : 14th February, 1998

Father's Name : Shri Niwas Sharma

Nationality : Indian

Marital Status : Married

Languages Known : English & Hindi

Address: A-63, Naveen Vihar, Begampur, Delhi-110086.

(Mohit Sharma)